export const data = [
    {
      question: "Which device is required for the Internet connection?",
      option1: "Modem",
      option2: "Router",
      option3: "LAN Cable",
      option4: "Pen Drive",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which continent has the highest number of countries?",
      option1: "Asia",
      option2: "Europe",
      option3: "North America",
      option4: "Africa",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Junk e-mail is also called?",
      option1: "Spam",
      option2: "Fake",
      option3: "Archived",
      option4: "Bin",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "A computer cannot BOOT if it does not have the?",
      option1: "Application Software",
      option2: "Internet",
      option3: "Operating System",
      option4: "Mouse",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "First page of Website is termed as?",
      option1: "Index Page",
      option2: "Homepage",
      option3: "Sitemap",
      option4: "Pen Drive",
      ans: 2,
    },

    {
      question: "Which is the correct way to create a React component?",
      option1: " function Hello() { return <h1>Hello world </h1>",
      option2: "const Hello = <h1>Hello World</h1>",
      option3: "React.createComponent('Hello',()=><h1> Hello World </h1>);",
      option4: "const Hello = <h1>Hello World</h1>",
      ans: 1,
    },

     {
      question: " Which Hook is used to manage state in functional components?",
      option1: " useProps",
      option2: "useState",
      option3: "useEffect",
      option4: "useContext",
      ans: 2,
    },
    
    {
      question: "  Which of the following is true about props?",
      option1: " Props are mutable ",
      option2: "Props can only be used in class components",
      option3: "Props can directly change state",
      option4: "Props are passed from parent to child",
      ans: 4,
    },

        {
      question: " In which file do you generally define routing in React (with react-router) ?",
      option1: " App.js ",
      option2: "index.html",
      option3: "Router.js",
      option4: "public/index.js",
      ans: 1,
    },
    
     {
      question: " What method is used to render React components into the DOM?",
      option1: "ReactDOM.start()",
      option2: "React.mount()",
      option3: "ReactDOM.render()",
      option4: "React.renderComponent()",
      ans: 3,
    }, 

  ];